Ali Asim

Pakistan



aliasimhussain22@gmail.com



+923362331707



linkedin.com/in/ali-asim-497840194

Summary

Hello! Welcome to my page, I'm a Senior Project Manager who is a specialist in website and logo projects. I'm Experienced in all sorts of website building platforms such as WordPress, Shopify, Wix, and many more. My background in Computer Science allows me to handle most technicalities in the project. I have strong command in Customer Satisfaction and Support.

Experience



Business Unit Manager

Logic-Unit

Jan 2022 - Present (3 months +)



Associate Manager

Technified Labs Jun 2021 - Feb 2022 (9 months)

Assistant Manager

Digitonics labs (Pvt.) Itd Mar 2020 - Jun 2021 (1 year 4 months)



Intern Information Technology Department

SUI SOUTHERN GAS COMPANY

Sep 2019 - Oct 2019 (2 months)

Education



PAF-Karachi Institute of Economics & Technology

Bachelor of Computer Science, Computer Programming 2017 - 2021



PECHS Government Science College

Intermediate, Pre-Engineering 2014 - 2016



Happy Palace Grammar School

Olevels, Engineering 2006 - 2014

Licenses & Certifications

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing - Google NA5 UZJ B4B

Google Cloud Platform Essentials

Baseline: Data, ML, AI - Qwiklabs

Skills

Customer Relationship Management (CRM) • Sales Management • Account Management • Digital Marketing • Computer Science • Project Management • Project Planning • Sales Operations • Social Media Marketing • Adobe Photoshop